[Music]
our parents are weird now right I have
kids man I have kids and I'm generation
between two generations so I'm taking
care of my kids and my parents at one
point I had four in diapers and two of
them were my parents yeah everybody got
nervous on the diaper stuff lotta guys
are in your 20s look how beautiful you
are all perfect and shiny 50 years from
now if diapers every one of us that's if
it works out that's best case scenario
so my mother and father haven't spoken
to each other in 30 years and a year ago
they both went into assisted living at
the same time I had to help them because
I'm the sibling who takes care of the
parents so I'm taking care of the
parents and so it's hard if you've ever
done assisted living with an elder
family member than you know it's not
easy time-consuming heart-wrenching
expensive for me times two because they
don't talk to each other so I was
holding out hope for the dementia would
kick in and they'd lose their memory and
I could put them into 2-bedroom
apartment together and film that as a
reality show
you'd binge watch the crazy old parents
who don't know how to hate each other
shelf
I don't know how you know my middle name
and I'm gonna find out Oh weird now my
father is 83 he thinks computers aren't
going to work out tell me that don't
waste your money son the whole thing's a
scam he printed up an email and sent it
to me in the mail he won't get an email
address because that's how they get your
information and then there know exactly
where you are all the time like you
haven't left the house in seven months
everybody knows exactly where you are
all the time quick sending me letters
with human handwriting on them it's
creepy everything's automated now we
have email and the post office at the
same time we're going to have to explain
that in four decades to our grandkids
that we simultaneously had email in the
post office that's going to blow their
mind if you like grandpa buck was paper
it was made from tree
well--we're dreams grandpa not important
son we got oxygen tanks now screw almond
don't need them anymore you'd write a
little letter on a piece of paper and
then you'd fold it up and put it inside
of another piece of paper that had a
little door on it now is called an
envelope some people called it an
envelope those people will will reject
and you take your letter to a dangerous
uncomfortable place called a post office
you'd wait around for hours in the body
odor and the lack of eye contact till
you finally got to talk to an angry miss
shapen man who lived with his mother and
had an inexpensive haircut that man
would sell you a little sticker you
could put on your envelope but you'd
lick it and get cancer and give it right
back to it that's when they would
deliver my letter notes on a bunch of
stuff happened after that they're
shoving a slot in the back wall where
there are more hangry people from bad
family those trolls that put it on an
airplane who travel hither and yon
across the country sometimes for weeks
till someone finally discovered it was
on the wrong aircraft
and that's when they would delivered no
son not yet that's when they would
accidentally deliver us to the neighbor
of the person that's you sent it to in
the first place
the madman based on his relationship
with his neighbor who decide whether or
not that scumbag was gonna get his mail
[Laughter]